throughout this part we supposed to start obviously you realize the lectures are videotaped that's
在这部分中，我们应该开始
显然，您意识到讲座被录像了，这就是为什么我必须开始
why I have to start exactly 1213 I suppose I have your permission with the
恰好是1213年，我想我已经允许您使用磁带了，我们不是
tape here we are not actually in the video but if you say anything also
实际上在视频中，但如果您说什么
you don't have to worry because
您也不必担心，因为它不会让您起床
it's not going to pick you up very micro points which made but the lectures
提出的要点，但讲座将被录像并张贴在
are going to be videotaped and posted on the  website of the course and also on what's  the system
课程的网站以及系统是什么
但是您知道我们发布了YouTube上的讲座，因此您可以下载它们
but you know we put the lectures from YouTube so you can download them directly
from the next notes the course
但是您知道我们发布了YouTube上的讲座，因此您可以下载它们
直接从下一个注释中得知该课程的网站正在建设中
website it's an under construction which means it's only the link is there the rest
意味着只有链接存在，当我设法
is going to be up when I managed to
get some sleep of 12 hours deadlock okay so maybe tomorrow or something you know
意味着只有链接存在，当我设法
睡上12个小时的僵局，好吧，也许明天或
get some sleep of 12 hours deadlock okay so maybe tomorrow or something you know
在下一次演讲之前您肯定知道的一些东西，我希望有这个东西
certainly before the next lecture I hope to have this thing up with today's lecture
以及今天的讲座和视频，让我们来看看
and video as well let's see the glass is Tuesdays and Thursdays 12:32 unqualified I
玻璃杯是星期二和星期四12:32不合格我知道已经有
know there has been lots of changes from the timing it's really not something I
从时间上开始发生了很多变化，这实际上不是我在您掌控的时候
control when you use the lecture room like 126 the Bartolo that has videotaping you
使用像126这样的Bartolo的演讲室
know everybody wants this room so it's very difficult to watch that yes everything is
每个人都想要这个房间，所以很难看
是的，一切都在进行，谢谢，感谢您的光临
on yeah thank you thanks for stopping by so this room is on high demand
所以这个房间的需求很高，所以我们进来然后进进出出，所以
so we were in then we were out in and out so we are in
as of today the Baku next
所以这个房间的需求很高，所以我们进来然后进进出出，所以
截止到今天，我们位于巴库下一个救援站的第一名，也许不是
rescue station first place and maybe not every Friday but once a while we're going
每个星期五，但不定期有一次朗诵，让我们
to have recitations to get we've
helped with a homework and in addition when there are missing lecture I'm going to
每个星期五，但不定期有一次朗诵，让我们
帮助做功课，此外，当缺少讲座时，我要去
use cry this to cover up for that so
用这个来掩饰这一点，让我们看看那是我的电子邮件
let's see what else that's my email address whatever information you need I want to
解决您需要的任何信息，我想尝试在课程中提供
try to provide it on the course
website okay there's a lots of there you know regarding the course objectives this is
解决您需要的任何信息，我想尝试在课程中提供
网站上有很多关于课程目标的知识
website okay there's a lots of there you know regarding the course objectives this is
这不是通常不教应用程序的应用程序课程权利
not an application course right that don't usually teach application of courses so Vista course
课程，因此Vista课程是关于社区图形学的基础的
on the fundamentals of community graphical modules and I remember someone's had asked me in
模块，我记得过去有人问过我，你知道那是什么
the past you know what's probabilistic graphical models thinking must be something graphical you know
概率图形模型思考必须是您所知道的图形事物
probably the graphical models is a
图形模型可能是一个常数，但是可以与许多模型一起使用
constant yet is a way to work with many random variables and if you think
随机变量，如果您认为许多有价值的内容以某种方式
this many of the valuable some somehow interconnected because they are correlated there is a
相互关联，因为它们相互关联，存在一个图，然后
graph and then maybe we can do some graph theoretic approaches to doing transpose but
也许我们可以做一些图论的方法来进行转置，但是不要
don't expect to have a problem where there is a graph and then you say
期望有一个有图的问题，然后您说哦做某事
oh do something with this graph the graph is there all right so you have
有了这个图，这个图就可以了，所以您必须考虑一些事情
to think of something being represented as a graph and I think it comes tense
被表示为图形，我认为这是最困难的
that's the most difficult part of of the of the cost being able to actually
成本的一部分能够
visualize on how what is a good
实际形象地看待如何用一个好的模型来表示两者之间的关系
model to represent the relations between many other body okay so I'm going to try
很多其他身体还可以，所以我将尝试为您提供所有基本知识
to give you all the fundamentals to do
inference in graphs and when I talk about the interest rate refer to Bayesian inference
很多其他身体还可以，所以我将尝试为您提供所有基本知识
图的推论，当我谈到利率时，指的是
inference in graphs and when I talk about the interest rate refer to Bayesian inference
贝叶斯推理，我将讨论有向图和无向图
I'm going to discuss both directed and undirected graphs maybe people in social science do
也许社会科学领域的人们会做他们喜欢有向图的心理学
psychology they like directed graph people in science and engineering the like undirected graphs but
科学和工程领域的人喜欢无向图，但是我们已经
we've received some how we can connect the different types of graphs we learned one
收到了一些我们如何连接不同类型图的知识，我们学到了一个
all the types quite easily obviously you
所有类型都非常容易，很明显，您知道我将在这里给您提供示例
know I'm going to give you examples here and there represent the potential of using
并代表了使用标准图形模型的潜力
graphical models from standard machine learning problems the computer vision to doing scientific computing two
机器学习中的计算机视觉问题，以做科学计算两个
我没有自然语言处理计算生物学的认证
certifications of natural language processing computational biology I don't  believe we have anybody from biology the  audience do we  okay
相信我们有来自生物学的人吗？
好的
certifications of natural language processing computational biology I don't  believe we have anybody from biology the  audience do we  okay
显然没有人做任何与事情类型有关的事情，所以我们没有
obviously nobody does anything related to the type of things so we don't have anything
今年学生的任何贡献，当然，课程是
any contributions from students this year right well the course is appropriate basically for students
基本上适合数学统计学和计算机科学的学生
in math statistics and computer science for students in engineering that have good mathematical skills
工程专业的学生，​​他们具有良好的数学技能，但非常相关
but very relevant and students in all areas of time this including cognitive sciences biology
以及所有时间领域的学生，包括认知科学生物学
if it's called chemical etc some of this course is to not universally so popular
这叫做化学等，这门课程的某些部分并不普遍流行
I'd noticed for example you go to
我注意到例如你去斯坦福大学
Stanford the cost is more than click on the students attending again because there is
费用比点击再次参加的学生还多，因为那里
interest from every direction ok here
是来自各个方向的兴趣，好吧，这里有选择性的不是
you have the selective ones are not the same we have the carrots to come
同样，我们也有胡萝卜要来参加这些在德里和我的讲座
and attend these lectures to Delhi and I hope to see you on with the
希望能在星期四的下一场演讲上见到你，好吧，我希望
next lecture on Thursday as well okay and I hope to see you the day
我第一次做作业后的第二天见，因为通常是
after I give the first homework because usually that's when the class population goes down
班级人口下降了50％好吧B这不是导致我们
by 50% okay now B this is not that caused us to get four credits
得到4个学分，我假设您唯一的原因是因为您想要
I am assuming you only reason you're here is because you want to learn the
学习主题并与您的研究相结合，我将为您提供帮助
topic and integrated with your research and I'm going to help you in doing that
but if you just need four
学习主题并与您的研究相结合，我将为您提供帮助
这样做，但是如果您只需要四个学分，这是正确的选择
credits this is on the right course for you okay I want to you know
你好，我想知道在许多方面这是一个非常重要的重要领域，
this is a very hot important area in many ways and I'm going to educate
我要教育您，但要了解这一点，您需要具备
you but to be able to learn this you need to have and interest from
如果没有的话，请不要从顶部获取兴趣，这不是一个值得关注的地方
the top if you don't this is not the place to be now the cost
you know it's going to be
如果没有的话，请不要从顶部获取兴趣，这不是一个值得关注的地方
现在您知道的费用将成为新课程的核心课程之一
one of the core courses from the new center for informatics and computational science is
信息和计算科学中心基本上是第二个
basically the second in sequence from a course to PI I taught on Bayesian statistics
从课程到PI的顺序，如果您在秋天，我会教贝叶斯统计
in the fall if you don't really need the previous course and if you need
真的不需要上一门课程，如果您需要什么，我的意思是
something well I mean when I say you don't need it you need everything right
当我说您不需要它时，您就需要正确的一切，而且您知道的越多，
the more you know the better but I cannot expect you that you know what
更好，但我不能指望您知道以前的内容
was covered to the previous course so when there are some fundamental concepts that we
当然，当我们需要一些基本概念时
need to bring in I will either cover them in this course where I will
带进来，我将在本课程中介绍它们，我会告诉你
give you know it's basically to read about them I think and it is possible
基本上是我想念他们，我可能会
that I'm gonna go back to you some of the topics covered in the poll
无论如何，请回头再讲一些本次调查中涉及的主题，但请尝试
anyways but try to address them in a graph theoretic wonder okay so new algorithmic
在图论理论上解决它们，所以我们解决了新的算法问题
problems we cover for example related to data stimulation so you need to know probability
例如涉及与数据刺激有关的内容，因此您需要了解
您对概率周期一无所知的概率理论
theory you don't know anything about probabilities period will disappoint you you need to know
令人失望的是，您至少需要了解拉斯维加斯的规则和
the fundamentals at least Vegas rules and the lights about Bayesian inference and if we
有关贝叶斯推理的信息，如果我们已经介绍过
have taken even an introductory cost to must in learning may be useful okay machine
学习必须付出的代价可能会有用
对我而言，机器学习意味着计算统计
learning for me means computational statistics so whatever we need I will bring it back
因此，无论我们需要什么，为了您的方便，我都会将其取回，但这将
for your convenience but it is going to
be helpful if you have a book in your desk but you can look for
因此，无论我们需要什么，为了您的方便，我都会将其取回，但这将
如果您的书桌上有一本书会很有帮助，但是您可以查找信息
information okay and I'm going to give you lots of readings that you can go
好的，我将为您提供很多阅读材料，您可以通过这些内容
through this semester and also after the course is over you need to know programming
学期以及课程结束后，您需要了解编程
because we will make an effort every
因为我们会尽一切努力，每个作业都没有计算能力
homework didn't have a computational problem and we're going to try to do this even
问题，即使是在第一次作业中，我们也将尝试这样做
on the first homework these are the first home mortgage deduction calculations but what going
是第一个房屋抵押贷款扣除额的计算方法，但是
sort of to try to give you a computer assignment simply because we you know
尝试给您分配计算机只是因为我们知道我们想要
we want to precise this because that these computers is not to do ten calculations
精确地说，因为这些计算机不进行十次计算
there's too much you know computation
您知道太多计算了，而十个计算都没有被试着去
and ten calculations were not tempted to  do any serious problems okay all right
做任何严重的问题好吗
就像在秋季学期依靠法院周围其他人的帮助一样
like in the fall semester of relying on the help from others around the court
so dr. Rubik Chakraborty this neck you
就像在秋季学期依靠法院周围其他人的帮助一样
所以博士卢比克·查克拉博蒂（Rubik Chakraborty）这条脖子，你知道那边有他的印记是
know the over there with his mark is going is volunteering to help with some
正在自愿帮助一些植被准备一些
of the vegetation preparing some of the
homework solutions and also doing some of the grading and so he's gone around the
正在自愿帮助一些植被准备一些
作业解决方案以及一些评分，所以他走了
resistance and maybe once if I give
阻力，如果我出门在外时要讲一两次课，也许有一次
a lecture or two when I'm out of town so the homework is going to
作业将以电子方式提交到该电子邮件地址，我是
be submitted electronically to this email address I'm going to provide more information on the
您将需要在封面上的网站上提供更多信息
website in the cover that you need to
submit the homework this address may change actually by tomorrow that's why I said this
您将需要在封面上的网站上提供更多信息
提交作业，此地址到明天可能会实际更改，这就是为什么我
email address this is a Google
说过此电子邮件地址，这是一个Google电子邮件帐户，但您可能已经
email account but you may have made  design one just for this class okay
为这个班级设计一个就可以了
我注意到你们中有些人看起来很疲倦哦，是的，您知道我们喜欢打字作业，因为
I notice some of you look worn oh yes you know we like typed homework
because it is for me especially computational silence and writing by 10:00 there's no way
我注意到你们中有些人看起来很疲倦哦，是的，您知道我们喜欢打字作业，因为
对我来说，尤其是计算的沉默和10:00之前的写作
we can figure out what you're
我们可以找出您在此处写的内容的方式
writing there if you write if you type something nice to me it is very
对我来说很棒的事情很容易知道发生了什么
easy to know what is going on okay so indeed with preferred type homework but
所以确实有喜欢的类型的作业，但是有些懒惰，我指的是
some of your lazy and I'm referring
to my students my own students so for those who are lazy you can stop
所以确实有喜欢的类型的作业，但是有些懒惰，我指的是
对我的学生我自己的学生，所以对于那些懒惰的人，你可以阻止你
the you can stick on your homework and stormy if there's a PDF attachment okay
如果有PDF附件，可以继续做作业，并且可以风雨如磐
if you do this thing's might can't ask me you will identify 90% of the
这件事可能不会问我，您将识别出90％的错误
mistakes in your homework just by typing it slowly and looking at it say oh
只需慢慢输入作业然后看一下就可以了，哦，看起来不
it doesn't look good and it doesn't look good mint is wrong okay but if
好，看起来也不好薄荷是不对的，但是如果你用手绑的话
you tied by hand it never looks good so you never have lost is it
永远看起来都不好，所以您永远不会迷失方向，因为大多数时候
right because most of the time is
wrong okay so we learnt that convert not to mention you know what if you
永远看起来都不好，所以您永远不会迷失方向，因为大多数时候
错误好吧，所以我们了解到转换不用说您知道如果您键入
type this nice 3 tomorrow you go for a job interview and you say yeah
这个不错的3明天你去求职面试，你说是的，我接受了这个
I took this course and here is what I did and that counts a lot
当然，这就是我所做的，这很重要，因为这不是
ok because this is not intro to happy hour type of port let's see the
介绍欢乐时光类型的端口，让我们看看如何使用
information on how you have to uch your homeworks and how to name
先生，请触摸一下您的作业以及如何再次命名您的提交内容
touch your homeworks and how to name your submission again sir I will give that
我要从不同网站开始的MOOC网站的信息
information of the website MOOCs I'm gonna start actually in different orders from what is
迈克尔·乔丹（Michael Jordan）的这本书给出的命令和介绍
given here the this book by Michael Jordan and introductions published graphical models is actually
实际使用的是已发布的图形模型
what is used in most universities for breeding and it's actually turtlecom you know everybody's
大多数大学都是育种动物
你知道每个人在准备转载这本书时的口味
taste in preparation reprint this book has been in preparation for 25 years which means
准备25年，这意味着乔纳森教授已经放弃了
professor jonathan has given up basically because things are changing so rapidly it's like what's
基本上是因为事情变化如此之快，这就像
the point of finishing this book now okay and so versus actually the easiest and
现在完成这本书还可以，因此与实际上最简单，最实用的书相比
the most insightful reading that you can have and for those who register in the
您可以获得的有见地的阅读，以及对于那些在课程中注册的人的阅读
course I am going to send you a PDF so I shouldn't be saying this
将要发送给您PDF，所以我不应该出于信仰而这样说
on faith somehow you've been going to library find it okay all right the let's
不知何故，您一直在去图书馆找到它，好吧，让我们看看是否
see if you really want to do research in this area a heavy book that
您真的想在这方面进行一本厚实的书的研究
you need to have in your desk is the textbook by Colin is written is
在你的桌子上是科林写的教科书，写着一千多页
more than a thousand pages maybe 1,200 pages has a lot of information some we
也许1,200页有很多信息，我们将在其中涵盖
will cover it in this course in detail some all the details you don't need
本课程详细介绍了一些您不需要的细节，但需要加强
them but toughen the vistas the state of the art both in theory and algorithms
在理论和算法上都可以看到最先进的技术，因此您可以
so business you know recommended book basically or you know to have the the textbook
基本上知道推荐的书，或者你知道
拥有我们去年秋天通常适合凯文·拉什迪（Kevin Rushdie）编写的教科书，
that we usually fit last fall by Kevin Rushdie has you know it's like an
知道这就像一本机器学习百科全书，实际上不是
encyclopedia of machine learning it's not really a readable text book but it has lots
可读的教科书，但它具有许多新算法，但仍然更加现代
of new algorithm still much more modern Abroad's and it has a structural also that
在国外，它的结构也与
goes with all the examples in the
book which I recommend it right and it is actually less probabilistic than for example
在国外，它的结构也与
我建议正确的书，实际上它的概率比
book which I recommend it right and it is actually less probabilistic than for example
例如约旦的转载好吧，它喜欢使用点估计
Jordan's reprint okay it used likes to use point estimates for fast inference for most
大多数算法的快速推论，但是你知道我有
of the algorithms but you know there are I don't know six seven chapters are
不知道六七个章节正在考虑发布的图形模型
thinking for published graphical models and we will cover at least the essential parts of
我们至少将在这一章中介绍这些内容的关键部分
those this of just one chapter
on probabilistic graphical models that is actually an ideal read if you want to know
我们至少将在这一章中介绍这些内容的关键部分
在概率图形模型上，如果您想
on probabilistic graphical models that is actually an ideal read if you want to know
在我们开始采取良好立场之前，先了解一下该法院的所有情况，让我们
everything about this court before we even start to get a good stance let's say
this week is to read what's after is
在我们开始采取良好立场之前，先了解一下该法院的所有情况，让我们
说这个星期是要读之后的内容，所以即使你是分开的
it a a so if you're in separate even just without the details alright just
只要没有细节就可以了，它将为您服务
going through it it would serve you
extremely well because it has everything not loops or anything like that but has the
只要没有细节就可以了，它将为您服务
非常好，因为它的所有内容都没有循环或类似的内容，但具有
lots of insights as to what
关于什么是概率图形模型有很多见解，
probabilistic graphical models are and how to go about okay so certainly this would be
怎么做还可以，所以当然这将是一个好的开始
a good start point and also if he has the cube has many other things
点，如果他有立方体，还有很多其他东西可以利用
that utilized the machinery of probabilistic graphical models that we will also use in this
概率图形模型的机制，我们还将在此使用
课程16可读性最强的机器上最易读的书
course 16 readable most probably the most readable book on machine learning in the market
在市场上学习，甚至看了大约20年的身高，您会发现我
and even watched about 20 years tall you will find it I pressed when I
read it every other day I
在市场上学习，甚至看了大约20年的身高，您会发现我
当我隔天阅读它时，我感到很压力，所以我在那里找到了新的东西，所以我
find something new there okay and so I obviously I recommend all of this book
显然，我推荐这本书的所有评分，所以我们将有六个
okay grading so we're going to have six
homework the homework will be 60% of the grades and it be a project 40%
显然，我推荐这本书的所有评分，所以我们将有六个
家庭作业家庭作业占年级的60％，部分项目占40％
for some maybe that's too much you know but if you think about it no
也许您知道的太多了，但是如果您考虑一下，就没有考试，没有仪表，没有
总决赛没事，所以这是一个循序渐进的过程
exams no meters no finals nothing okay so this is a gradual course we don't
我们不采用经典的方式，但是期望比给予更高
operate the classical way but the expectations are higher than giving an example you write
一个例子，您写错了一些页面，表示祝贺我们通过
something wrong page that say congratulations we pass the course right so the project it
当然是正确的课程，所以我们必须更改项目，然后离开它
the program we have to change the leave it from those who took the course
来自那些参加民意测验的人，因为我很失望
in in the poll because I was very disappointed with the attitude of many students
在这里，许多学生对课程的态度
here when it comes to the course to the project I get freedom to everybody
我有自由给每个人定义的项目
to define their own project relevant to the course and I can tell you there
他们自己的课程相关项目，我可以告诉你至少有
were at least seven students who came up with a new definition of the project
七个学生提出了该项目的新定义，大约三个
about three days before the presentation I mean asked not normal just ridiculous okay so
演讲前几天我的意思是问不正常只是可笑
so I don't know exactly how
好吧，所以我不知道我们要怎么做，但我想
we're going to do it but I'm gonna think in the next two or three
在接下来的两三个星期内，但实际上
weeks but the possibility would be to actually literally five you ten twenty projects and
从字面上看，五个您十个二十个项目，并将其保存到Z，这是
save it to Z and here are the
references become whatever you like and do one of those and you cannot say right
从字面上看，五个您十个二十个项目，并将其保存到Z，这是
引用变成您喜欢的东西，并做其中之一，您不能说
well we may do it as last fall but
好的，我们可能会在去年秋天这样做，但是您必须更改严格的准则
with strict guidelines that you changed project means you get zero breaking your project we
项目意味着您零破坏项目
cannot allow basically a week before
我们基本上不能允许代表在一周前巩固自己的
the representation solidifying what the project is and I'm not talking about the trying a
项目是，我不是在谈论我正在谈论的尝试
little bit I'm talking about going from A to Z okay not to mention going
从A转到Z好，更不用说从A到Z和SIF没有
from A to Z and SIF having no
relation to the course at all right so that's number I take so certainly I
从A转到Z好，更不用说从A到Z和SIF没有
完全与课程相关，所以我要选择这个数字，所以我当然想要
want with the project to give you an opportunity to do something that is relevant
该项目使您有机会做一些有意义的事情
to your research right so that
与您的研究权相关，这样您不仅会因为学习而受益
not only you benefit because you learn the material of the course for those strong
该课程对于那些坚强的您有益的材料，因为该课程在
you benefit because the course in
fact you're already served and that's very important okay so now because of so the
该课程对于那些坚强的您有益的材料，因为该课程在
其实你已经服役了，这很重要，所以现在，因为
the project is going to require a
该项目将需要一份不限于六页的报告
report which is not limited to six pages a written presentation like PowerPoint of Beamer
书面演示文稿，例如Beamer的PowerPoint和另一个演示文稿，以及
and another presentation and because we have two dates in the fall with scheduling with
因为我们在秋天有两个约会安排我们的演讲
our presentations and videotaping them have not seen any of the videos yet by the
和录制他们还没有通过艺术家的方式看过任何视频
way of artists presentations yet because they have not been provided to me but have
演示文稿，因为它们尚未提供给我，但拥有我们所拥有的
what we're going to do to avoid all that the next weekend we're going to
下个周末要避免一切，我们可能会采取
take maybe the last three or four lectures of the course and we're going to
课程的最后三到四节课，我们将要
have the presentations in class so you're going to be on this real video and
课堂上的演示文稿，这样您就可以观看这个真实的视频，而不是
not issue because the videos are automatic okay so we don't have to worry about
问题是因为视频是自动播放的，所以我们不必担心
story there's nothing available in May
故事可能没有可用的对不起
sorry in June this building is closed in July is open for something else and
在六月份，这座建筑关闭了，七月份关闭，其他的东西都开放了。
that we're gonna do it in class even if that takes lecture so be prepared
即使要上课，我们也会在课堂上做，所以要做好准备
the that the project would be you wave before the end of the semester the
该项目将是您在学期末之前挥手致意，意味着您的挥手致意
wave means you know three lectures of this before the end of the semester so
在学期末之前知道三堂课，所以我们要
we're gonna have to move on the projects quite strong okay the services are very
继续进行项目是很不错的，服务是非常初步的
preliminary so some of these topics we may cover them in lots of details but
因此，其中一些主题我们可能会涵盖很多细节，而有些则不会
some not we're going to discuss as I mentioned directive of the undirected graph this
我们将要讨论的是我提到的无向图的指令
should be of interest to everybody but
应该引起所有人的兴趣，但主要是您在社交和社交方面都知道
mainly you know in social and in social sciences natural language modeling things I thought
科学自然语言建模的东西，我认为市场模型是
market models are basically essential for people to work in scientific applications we're going to
对于人们从事科学应用工作而言，这基本上是必不可少的
do it lots of 12 hours for data
从开始就需要花费12个小时来处理数据模拟问题
simulation problems starting with basically a little relating everything that you may already know from
基本上把您可能已经从其他人那里知道的一切都联系了起来
other courses or not some of these topics we cover them and in the fall
课程或不涉及这些主题中的某些主题，我们会在秋季进行介绍，因此对于
so ideas for example of doing dynamical systems with particle methods now we will see
用粒子方法做动力系统的例子现在，我们将看到如何
how to develop the same identical algorithms but with a graph theoretic approach so for
开发了相同的算法，但是采用了图论方法
example you can think of doing
例如，您可以考虑进行卡尔曼滤波和泛化
Kalman filtering and generalization always with no effort using algorithms on graphs nothing new but
总是毫不费力地在图上使用算法
没什么新奇的，但滑倒的危险会使您的通货紧缩行动发展
the risk of slipping would grass you babel action to develop your own Oliver effect
您自己想要的Oliver效果，您希望标准方法的这种扩展
you want to that this extension of standard methodologies  that have been around for thirty years
已经存在三十年了
我们可能要花费超过两个讲座的时间，从五到五分钟不等
we're gonna spend maybe more than two lectures may be anything from five to ten
十场讲座，讨论图形推论和严格的概念
lectures to discuss inference in graphs and this concept of exacting first of course is
首先当然是您知道这并不总是可能的，所以我们要开始
you know it's not always possible so we are gonna start with this and then
有了这个，然后我们将覆盖作为当前想法的一部分，因此
we will so we will cover as part of exactly current idea so far the
到目前为止，新的传播破坏预算法消除和光将
new propagation destruction pre algorithm elimination and the light will discuss about approximate inference using
使用您所知道的均值的一般化讨论近似推论
generalizations of means you know means till the type of algorithms so this is an
意味着直到算法的类型，所以这是一个重要的领域，它
important area and it actually an earlier that literally goes coefficient with graph theoretic algorithms
实际上是从理论上讲与系数相关的更早版本
so this will be an essential
算法，这将是成本的重要组成部分，如果有时间，我会
part of the cost and if we have time I think maybe we spend two
想想也许我们会花两个三堂课来讨论您如何学习
three lectures to discussed on how do you learn the structure of a graph so
图的结构，所以如果有人花了几个小时查看实现
if somebody for hours view realizations for a few hundred of variables and you want
百个变量，您想弄清楚它们之间的关联方式
to figure out how they are correlated how do we do this how do you
我们这样做吗？您如何想出图和图的学习破坏
come up with learning destruction of a graph and of course we've realized the this
当然我们已经意识到这是一个非常困难的开放问题，所以这是
is a very difficult open problem right so this is actually the fantastic area to
实际上是做博士的理想领域，而不是一件P，您可以工作100
do a PhD not one piece P you can work for 100 feet this because
因为我不相信这个问题可以解决
I don't believe this problem can be scaled many of the variables alright but it's
好多变量都可以，但这是一个重要的话题
an important topic that is to be
discussed so the lectures will give in the tape I think we think an hour
好多变量都可以，但这是一个重要的话题
讨论，所以讲座将在录音带中，我想我们认为一个小时的两个
two of the lectures are available on Sakai when the website is up if not
如果今天不上网站的话，在Sa市上可以使用的讲座
today tomorrow we will post these videotapes the on YouTube so will be that youtube
我们会将这些录像带发布到YouTube上，以便该youtube链接
link where the lecture PDFs will be posted I hesitate actually have to think about
我会毫不犹豫地考虑将讲座PDF发布到何处
this if I want to post the lectures like
如果我想像秋天那样发布讲座，以便您参加
we did in the fall so that you have them in front of you during
在讲课期间在您面前，因为我观察到某些
the lectures because I was observing certain individuals in this room but they are still
个人在这个房间里，但他们仍然很清楚
clear okay during my lectures basically doing nothing else but just looking on that computer
在我的演讲中，基本上什么也没做，只是看着
that's not the way to go I mean
电脑不是走的路我的意思是你为什么要知道我的意思是
why have you you know I mean they are looking at bookkeeping you can look
查看簿记，您可以查看表格，因为业务将
at form right since the business will be available this you need to come to
可得到的，您需要向他们求助，我的意思是，当然，如果
them I mean make me spill good of course if you come and I appreciate
你来了，我很感激，但我认为这个主意是即使
but I think the idea is to be able to benefit even partially by listening
可以通过亲自听这些讲座来部分完成，但是可以肯定的是
in person to these lectures okay but for sure the lectures will be positive if
如果您知道之后不久就去听讲座，那将是积极的
not before immediately after you know you know in the afternoon of the same day
在同一天的下午，将会有很多参考文献和
there will be a lots of references of papers and books and things I got
我将获得的书籍和东西可以链接到讲座，因此请考虑将其作为
that I will link to the lectures so consider those as very useful readings and
非常有用的阅读材料，而且您还会有很多黑板链接
also there will be a lot of chalkboard links that you can use this well
可以很好地使用它，为什么我会忘记这个，因为我们是我想要的录像带
why would I forgot this because we're video tape I want to encourage questions but
鼓励提问，但我将不得不重复您的问题
I'm gonna have to repeat your questions otherwise nobody Houston anything okay so let me
否则没人会休斯敦没事，所以让我在那儿停下有关的任何问题
stop there any questions about the structure of it all really there's no structure I
这一切的结构真的没有结构，我的意思是我们做任何事情
mean we do anything we want to we can change our mind tomorrow all right
希望我们明天可以改变主意
we are interest money to learn and not
我们有兴趣学习的钱，而不是从A到B再到C，因为我在那里
to go from A to B to C because I there's no such a thing
okay so and feel free to
我们有兴趣学习的钱，而不是从A到B再到C，因为我在那里
没有这样的事情好吧，随时利用掉任何问题
take advantage drop any questions
当然，我要问的问题是，你们中有多少人会爱上我们
of course the question I have to ask is how many of you will love
星期四还好，我希望大家都还好
stick with us on Thursday alright and I hope everybody alright bring the cousins -
带来堂兄弟-好吧，我们需要我们所能获得的所有支持
okay we need all the support we can get
我的意思是我的一位学生现在正在普渡大学与该学生相似的课程中任教
I mean one of my students is teaching now at Purdue similar course as the
one without clearing in the fall more or less things are a little more basic
我的意思是我的一位学生现在正在普渡大学与该学生相似的课程中任教
没有在秋天清除或多或少的东西是基本的，但
but she told me she has more than 60 they had to limit the cluster
她告诉我她有60多个他们必须限制集群才能
talents was fixed it because they were students from every quarter interested but you know
修复它是因为他们是每个季度感兴趣的学生，但您知道
here we're a small population so we
这里的人口很少，所以我们没有60的营养
don't have the Nutri of 60 20 is actually a great number for example for
例如，实际上有很多可以，但是你们需要不要放弃
okay but you guys need to not to give up
when I give homework okay if you do give  up I'm sorry for you all right so no  questions
例如，实际上有很多可以，但是你们需要不要放弃
当我放弃功课好吗，如果你放弃的话，我为你感到抱歉，所以没有
when I give homework okay if you do give  up I'm sorry for you all right so no  questions
任何问题只是为了娱乐事物而已，而是以我所知的方式
any questions just to entertain the thing no but the way whichever I know who
have at least and students that will
任何问题只是为了娱乐事物而已，而是以我所知的方式
至少有和将要听的学生被阻止参加各种活动
be listening to be stopped from various places overseas okay I have been surprised the
海外的地方好吧，我很惊讶收到的名字
receiving names of students from certain universities in China but they even do the homework
来自中国某些大学的学生，但他们甚至做作业和
and they submit me corrections to the homework okay so and corrections to the software
他们向我提交了对作业的更正，对我的更正
of the homework the case though
作业的软件，虽然如此，但我已经看到了一些影响
and I have seen the impact some of this lectures have had on various health
关于各种健康的讲座，因此颇有收获
so it served quite rewarding okay so we're going to start with sort of some
好吧，我们将从一些基本的介绍开始
elementary introduction to control in a geographical borders discussing some terminology maybe one or two
地理边界中的控件讨论一些术语，可能是一个或
basic examples I am NOT gonna do any
两个基本示例我不会做任何数学线性问题或其他任何操作
mathematics linear questions or anything like that but so if you see saying things that
像那样，但是如果你看到真正说的话
really require a lot of explanations keep in mind and when I come back to
需要记住很多解释，当我回到这些解释时
those topics and discuss them in detail as we go along right so this is
主题，并在我们正确进行时进行详细讨论，因此，这仅是为了
just to give you a flavor of what a probabilistic graphical model is and what
您将了解概率图形模型是什么以及类型是什么
the type of promise were interested by the way in addition to the video lectures
除了视频讲座外，Promise也很感兴趣，如果来自
if from our course if you served with the constant form you say probabilistic graphical
我们的课程，如果您以不变的形式服役，那么您说的是概率论
图形模型，您可以从许多短法院系统中找到注释
models you will find notes from many short court system here have heroes living divani
生活在divani和圣诞节的英雄们进行了一系列的演讲
and Christmas of have a series of lectures on probabilistic graphical with videos and PDFs
带有视频和PDF的概率图形，但您知道
but you know you can find online the Stanford courses and many other universities the
可以在网上找到斯坦福课程以及许多其他课程
大学，康奈尔大学等课程，所以如果您有
courses from Cornell etc so you can sort of if you have questions with a
与某个主题相关的问题，如果您转身，您将可以找到很多东西
certain topic if you turn you'll be able to find a lot of resources I
资源，我认为这是机器学习的好地方，
think the good thing is this area of machine learning it's an area of a
一个非常开放的社会，喜欢外面的事物可以开放，好吧，我们
very open society that likes things out there to be open okay we don't hide
不要隐藏任何人都能真正受益的东西，我们喜欢这样
anything everybody can actually benefit and we like it that way
所以我们实际上是概率图形模型，只是用于建模关系
so we're really probabilistic graphical models just to model the relations between many random variables
在许多随机变量之间好吧，所以现在有效地将是
okay so now effectively would be a way to produce the joint probability of this
最产生这个物体的联合概率，所以X这里是一个向量，所以
body most so X here is a vector so the
probabilistic graphical models will give us sort of file an efficient way to model this
最产生这个物体的联合概率，所以X这里是一个向量，所以
概率图形模型将为我们提供一种有效的解决方案
probabilistic graphical models will give us sort of file an efficient way to model this
为该分布火灾事实建模，以及我们需要具备的能力
distribution fire fact and something that we would need to be able to take advantage
利用我们的脾气时，我们将能够
when we work with grouches we're going to be able to account for the independent
通过某种方式解释这些变量之间的独立关系
relations between these variables by somehow
从图上删除一些链接，如我们所愿，它很好，所以我有这些
dropping some links from the graph as we wish it softly all right so I
have these two variables and they're not connected darkus an implication probabilistically speaking so the
从图上删除一些链接，如我们所愿，它很好，所以我有这些
两个变量，它们没有连接起来，暗含概率
have these two variables and they're not connected darkus an implication probabilistically speaking so the
因此，这里的想法是，联合概率分布在
idea here would be that the joint probability distribution when it is factorized according to
它是根据图分解的，或者图不适合模型中的模型
a graph or a graph is not right the model in the police relations you
在这种可能性内您知道的警察关系
know inside this probability distribution if we do that we will be able to take
如果这样做，我们将能够利用推论的优势
advantage of inference algorithms but still very nicely in graphs all right and in some
算法，但在所有图表中以及在某些情况下仍然非常好
of the solvent you used completely graph theoretic sort of argument and so they are
您使用的溶剂完全是图论的论点，所以它们
very convenient now if somebody if
如果有人给我，现在很方便，如果我给你说50个变量
you if I give you let's say 50 variables and you learn the joint probability
您将学习联合概率分布，并以某种方式可以 某种不错的方式进行分解，主要的兴趣是进行推理
distribution and somehow you can factorize in some nice way the main interest will be
to do inference which means if I knowledge say this stand variables what's the probability
您将学习联合概率分布，并以某种方式可以 某种不错的方式进行分解，主要的兴趣是进行推理
意味着如果我知道说这个立场变数，
of very many variables all right and so we're going to have to do somehow
好多变量，所以我们将不得不做一些开发
develop some algorithms that will allow us to compute marginal and conditional distributions out of
允许我们计算边际和条件分布的算法
从这种联合分布中，我们应该能够做到的Adisa Teno联合
this joint distribution the Adisa Teno the joint we should be able to do lots
of things cheaply and in particular
从这种联合分布中，我们应该能够做到的Adisa Teno联合
很多东西便宜，尤其是现在的图形
that will be the case for graphs now when you have a joint distribution like
当您有这样的联合分布时，您将总是有很多
that you will always have lots of
unknown parameters to define the joint distribution so one of the tasks in probabilistic graphical
当您有这样的联合分布时，您将总是有很多
定义关节分布的参数未知，因此，其中一项任务
unknown parameters to define the joint distribution so one of the tasks in probabilistic graphical
概率图形模型是找出那些参数是什么
model is to figure out what those parameters are given realizations of some random variables
给定一些随机变量的实现，所以我们将看到示例
okay so we would see examples
of that
给定一些随机变量的实现，所以我们将看到示例
在那
of that
让我们走吧，大概女权主义者基本上是军事加图论的人
let's go so probably a feminist is basically for military plus graph theory okay we
好吧，我们显然不会删除它，因为
obviously we won't drop it because
we're graph speak we can visualize the independence relation between the many of the variables
好吧，我们显然不会删除它，因为
我们是图说话，我们可以可视化许多人之间的独立关系
and once we do that we
变量，一旦完成，我们就可以激发许多新算法
can motivate the lots of new algorithms I mean the posture can tell you when
我的意思是，当我有兴趣解决一些奇怪的问题时，这种姿势可以告诉您
I was interested in solving some weird multi scale problems I've as long as visualizing
我一直在想像多尺度的问题
of how this may look like
and everybody thought that was an idiot because somehow they couldn't see how probabilistic graphical
我一直在想像多尺度的问题
每个人都认为那是一个白痴，因为他们不知怎么
and everybody thought that was an idiot because somehow they couldn't see how probabilistic graphical
概率图形模型可能是相关的，但如果在这里，那么您
model can be relevant but if it is here then you should be able to
应该能够将其放入计算机程序中
put it in a computer program okay so visualizing the structure of a probability model
因此，可视化事物的概率模型的结构是必不可少的
of thing is essential to get nice algorithms all right so we're going to develop
为了获得好的算法，我们将开发一种算法，
algorithms that they take advantage of this graph structure so we're going to be able
他们利用了这种图结构，因此我们将能够
to do inference learning and all of these things affected in the graphs and the
做推理学习，所有这些事情都会影响到图表和
ideas for example of these masters
例如，这些大师通过算法的想法将是
passing algorithms will be something  that you cannot do without a graph  theoretic approach
没有图论方法就无法做到的
因此，在为实际以图形方式看起来的模型调整大小时所获得的好处是
so the benefit you get in sizing for the model you look actually graphically and
you can say lots of things as to how the
因此，在为实际以图形方式看起来的模型调整大小时所获得的好处是
关于变量周围如何与每个变量相关联，您可以说很多话
around the variables correlate to each other you can develop many new algorithms by playing
其他，您可以通过使用结构来开发许多新算法
with the structure of the graph and most of the inference we will do in
图和我们在本课程中所做的大多数推断都可以扩展
this course can scale nicely simply because of this independence relations but implied by by
恰好是因为这种独立关系，但是被
the gun action and actually I can tell
枪械动作，实际上我可以告诉你，这就是你不需要的全部
you that's quite all you don't need to know anything as a background all the
知道任何东西作为背景机器学习中总是有所有的计算
calculations always in machine learning there are nothing else but applications of the solid product
除了以下方面的固体产品规则的应用外，别无其他
rules of probability and we will see this something on Thursday when we develop simple
概率，我们将在周四开发时看到这一点
things on graphs so realist you
图上的简单事物如此真实，您知道概率的定义
know the definitions of probabilities and what the stomach for the fruits are then you
以及水果的胃是什么，那么您就可以做好很多准备了
are ready best bid to do lots
of nice things
以及水果的胃是什么，那么您就可以做好很多准备了
好东西
of nice things
但是我告诉过你，不要害怕，我会提出很多概念，因为我们会
but I told you that don't be scared I power lots of concepts because we
will develop all of this in separate lectures so I'm just throwing this as an
但是我告诉过你，不要害怕，我会提出很多概念，因为我们会
在单独的讲座中开发所有这些内容，所以我只是将其作为
introduction so the dart is going to
介绍，所以飞镖将编码任何独立性
encode the whatever independence assumptions exist for my many random variables all right and basically
我的许多随机变量都存在假设，基本上，我们将
we'll be able to factorize the probability distribution on the graph or given a graph
能够分解图上的概率分布或给定
we will know what type of
图，我们将知道该图符合哪种因式分解
factorization the graph complies for the probability distributions that we define the idea is that
我们定义这个想法的概率分布是
somehow this factorization of the joint probability distribution of the graph would be with local
图的联合概率分布的因式分解将是
functions that are defined on the
在图的注释上定义的局部函数，因此这些局部函数
notes of the graph so these local functions will be different things for directed graph
有向图的功能会有所不同，我们也称其为
which we also called the Bayesian networks and will be different for undirected graphs that
贝叶斯网络，对于无向图（也称为“无向图”）将有所不同
also we call them a mark of network okay but the idea is somehow a
他们是网络的标记，但想法是某种程度上的联合分布
joint distribution between many of our variables can be written as a product of local
我们的许多变量可以写成局部函数的乘积，这是
functions and this is great right but it's not so physically what you very did
很好，但实际上并不是您所做的那样，因为例如
because if for example you think spatially many of the variables the variables here don't
您认为空间上的许多变量这里的变量没有
depend on the volume is their right
取决于数量是他们的正确关联程度的局部范围
correlation sort of local extent so somehow if you can arrange these things to the
以某种方式，如果您可以将这些东西排列到图上，则您具有相似的本性
graph you have a similar nature
you will be able to do lots of work that is local and from these
以某种方式，如果您可以将这些东西排列到图上，则您具有相似的本性
您将能够通过这些本地功能完成许多本地工作
local functions you'll be able to say build this this joint distribution of the menu
您将可以说建立这个联合分布的
of the volumes by the way when
顺便说一句，当我说这里和那里的一些可穿戴设备时
I said some wearables of here and there this is in the special context or
这是在特殊情况下或在时间情况下，但哥特可能是一个非常
in the time context but the goth can be a very abstract entity they have
抽象实体，它们与时间无关，好吗，不是吗
nothing to do with space of time okay so don't you know again depending on
根据您感兴趣的事物的类型再次知道
the type of things you're interested you can envision different scenarios so Bayesian networks are
设想不同的情况，以便贝叶斯网络是概率图形
probabilistic graphical models that are defined on directed graphs and I'm gonna show you an
有向图上定义的模型，我将向您展示一个示例
example shortly and this Markov random pills this Markov networks are basically probabilistic graphical models
不久，这个Markov随机药丸这个Markov网络基本上是
无向图3的概率图形模型
for undirected graphs three so these are the main two types right and you can
主要两种类型，您可以有一些有向图
have some graphs that have some directed component some undirected components and also you can
组成一些无向的组成部分，你也可以以某种形式构成
pose this in sort of some
unified way using what's called photographs and we will discuss verse as well so actually
组成一些无向的组成部分，你也可以以某种形式构成
使用所谓的照片的统一方式，我们将以
unified way using what's called photographs and we will discuss verse as well so actually
好吧，实际上你知道三堂课
you know three lectures there's no point of discussion one type or another we will
没有讨论的重点，我们将统一开发一种或另一种
unify development for all of this at the same time okay the nodes in the
所有这些同时都可以，我们所代表的图中的节点是
graph we represent are the variables and this is very important the lack of transition
变量，这非常重要，因为缺少过渡图
the graph will imply conditional independence assumptions in other ways if I have nodes representing
如果我有其他方式暗示有条件独立性假设
代表随机变量的节点，我必须取十个变量，而我
random variables and I have to take ten variables and I connected smart evil with
将聪明的邪恶与其他身体世界联系起来，那么毫无意义
every other body world then there's no point of doing graphs because that problem complexity
做图，因为问题的复杂性永远不会让你走
will never allow you to go
anyway it's somehow some edges are missing that implies to military somebody who don't depend
做图，因为问题的复杂性永远不会让你走
无论如何，有些地方缺少了一些优势
anyway it's somehow some edges are missing that implies to military somebody who don't depend
对军人意味着不依赖地段的全部数量的人
on all the volume which the lots
what we need to think about so the idea is we are interested in graphs
对军人意味着不依赖地段的全部数量的人
我们需要考虑的问题，这样的想法是我们对图形感兴趣，
that they are not fully connected right they are fully connected one of gaining anything
没有完全连接正确，他们完全连接获得任何东西之一
by learning this course right the idea
通过正确学习这门课程，想法不是一切都取决于一切
is not everything depends on everything and we need to learn about part of the
我们需要了解我们讨论过的结构问题的一部分
structure problem that we discussed the
second part of the course but again the lack of threads is what represents conditional
我们需要了解我们讨论过的结构问题的一部分
课程的第二部分，但再次缺少线程是什么
second part of the course but again the lack of threads is what represents conditional
有条件的独立性假设，我们花了两三堂课
independence assumptions and we spend two or three lectures to discuss that and I will
讨论这个问题，我会给您一些正式的项目，以解决所有问题
give you a number of formal projects to work on all right so something just
好的，所以让我们从右边开始，这是一个有向图
let's go from right in there this is a directed graph I'm gonna give you
我将在后续幻灯片中为您提供术语，但只是
the terminology in of the you know in follow up slide but just to get
要使事情基本顺利进行，您可以使用常识解释
things going basically here you can use common sense interpretation for now you know so
现在您知道了，所有这些都是我们拥有的abcde的其他变量在两个
all of this are other variables we have a b c d e are on
two variables can be continuous or discrete doesn't really matter and the idea here of
现在您知道了，所有这些都是我们拥有的abcde的其他变量在两个
变量可以是连续的也可以是离散的，这并不重要，这里的想法
the service means that C depends
的服务意味着C依赖于今天，B依赖于C和D
today and B it depends on C and D right and so this implies this
所以这意味着箭头的这个方向是因果关系
direction of the arrow the causal relationship alright so big doesn't depend on me it
好吧，这么大不取决于我，取决于D，这是我从中了解到的
depends from D that's what I know from
here okay the rest you will need to derive from the factorization employed by this
好吧，这么大不取决于我，取决于D，这是我从中了解到的
好的，剩下的你需要从中得到
here okay the rest you will need to derive from the factorization employed by this
该指令模型采用的分解现在是这个方向
directive model now this one direction
graph there is no error okay so obviously if there's no arrows and you see
该指令模型采用的分解现在是这个方向
图没有错误就可以了，所以很明显，如果没有箭头，而您
graph there is no error okay so obviously if there's no arrows and you see
看到此连接显然C与aa和B有关
this connections obviously C is related to a a and B obviously she's related to
显然，她与您有关，并被羡慕，所以您的招数很严重
you and to be envied so you serious tricks there was this interconnected sets of
有这一系列相互关联的音符，所以两者都暗示着真正的相关性
notes so both imply really correlations
but there is no directional component so in essence the effect of EMV and BMC
有这一系列相互关联的音符，所以两者都暗示着真正的相关性
但没有方向性成分，因此从本质上讲，EMV和BMC的效果具有
has no direction okay so this is very different from what this chain is drawn
没有方向好，所以这与绘制此链有很大不同
好吧，现在我不再讨论这个
okay now I'm not going to discuss what this is in detail right but this
是详细的说明，但是这是另一种类型的图，它将使我们
is sort of another type of graph that will allow us to sort of unify
以便将这两个图形统一起来，并以某种方式做到这一点，我们需要
those two graphs okay and somehow to do that we need to introduce the sectional
引入分段平方的音符，但有效地明确说明这些
squared note but effectively explicitly spell out these local functions these local potentials but you
本地功能可以发挥这些本地潜力，但是您要么处于这种无方向性
have either in this undirected graphs or in the directed graphs so these are functional
图或有向图，所以这些功能正常，这就是为什么
and that's why this is called a photograph okay so this are the random variables
叫做照片好，所以这是随机变量，它是一个常数
and it's a constant okay and so we would be able to how to eventually
好的，所以我们将能够最终在因子图中进行推断
do inference in factor graphs and not way accounting for inference both directed and undirected
而不是再次考虑有向和无向模型的推论
model again you don't need to know anything any of this because we will spent
您不需要了解任何这些信息，因为我们将花费很多讲座
many lectures discussing each of this but I thought you should see this on lecture
讨论每一个问题，但我认为您应该在第一个演讲中看到
one so now is representative of variables edges dependencies and really what we're interested is
现在代表变量边依存关系，实际上是
in the lack of the edges
感兴趣的是缺少边缘，所以路径之间没有边缘
so the path but there is no edge between a and B that's very important
如果您尝试将A连接到B，将D连接到Eve，则a和B非常重要，
if you try to connect a to B to D to Eve than don't expect
不要期望通过做图理论方法获得任何收益
to gain anything by doing graph theoretic approach okay so in if you have many
因此，如果您有许多节点，那么这是这个村庄的高维
nodes so this is the trek high-dimensional this village h 100 the first objective when
100使用图形时，第一个目标是提出联合
you work with graphs is to come up with the joint probability distribution and in
概率分布，尤其是具有
particularly with the factorized form of
the joint probability distribution okay the fact is form that somehow can easily be visualized
概率分布，尤其是具有
联合概率分布还可以，事实是某种形式可以轻松实现的形式
the joint probability distribution okay the fact is form that somehow can easily be visualized
在图形中可视化，说明存在任何独立性关系
in a graph accounting for whatever independence relations exist between these values now you can
在这些值之间，您现在可以体会到，如果变量
appreciate that if the variables dependent there is no independence relations right and each of
依赖没有独立关系的权利，而这些独立关系中的每一个
these variables can take K values and let's say each of these columns is also
变量可以取K值，假设这些列中的每个
discrete and can take K values how many
离散的，可以取K个值，多少个值需要多少信息
values how much information you need to describe this probability distribution so you need K
描述这种概率分布，因此您需要为每个概率分配K个值
values for each of them and you have via block how many variables Divinity's try
并且您可以通过块查看Divinity尝试描述多少个变量
完全没有独立关系的这种联合分布
to describe this joint distribution with no independence relations at all
夺走力量
take away the power
电源B正确，所以至少有10个您忘记了您将无能为力
the power B right so it least 10 forget about you won't be able to
do anything okay so we will see on what we can benefit take and run
电源B正确，所以至少有10个您忘记了您将无能为力
好的，所以我们将看看我们可以从中受益并采取行动
up to this condition in the ventilation and drop now once somehow you can come
通风状况良好，现在就下降，一旦您可以想出
up with the proper authorization of this then you can stop talking about the inference
适当的授权，那么您就可以停止谈论推理了
so for example if you let's say measure
因此，例如，假设您要测量变量X 1的值，
the value of variable X 1 you have you know what the value is then
知道值是多少，那么在给定X 1的情况下，您可以保持x 2的值不变
you can stay with the value of x 2 given X 1 where the rest
of the variables maybe you want
知道值是多少，那么在给定X 1的情况下，您可以保持x 2的值不变
其余的变量也许您想分析一下就可以摆脱它们
analyze them ok to get rid of them so obviously you appreciate that the sum
所以很显然，您很欣赏总和和乘积法则对
and product rule will come candy to
actually manipulate this but also Bayes  rule would be essential when you have  evidence to be able to do inference
所以很显然，您很欣赏总和和乘积法则对
实际操纵它，但是当您拥有贝叶斯规则时，必不可少
actually manipulate this but also Bayes  rule would be essential when you have  evidence to be able to do inference
能够推理的证据
应用程序真的，您知道您刚才提到的任何内容都对
applications really you know you just mentioned any anything right so in diaphragmatic this standard
所以在横diaphragm膜这个标准方法在医学诊断中实际上
methods in in medical diagnosis actually
almost every you know diagnosis now actually every time I am reading articles but visual
所以在横diaphragm膜这个标准方法在医学诊断中实际上
现在几乎每次我阅读时，几乎每个您知道的诊断
almost every you know diagnosis now actually every time I am reading articles but visual
文章，但视觉化的疾病诊断系统将取材于
to make the systems for diagnosing diseases would take from images etc they operate with
图像等，它们发生误报的机会比最佳情况少得多
much less chance for false alarms than the best doctor in the world right they're
世界上的医生，他们非常准确，所以现在不像
extremely accurate so now it's not like
this is for mathematicians or computer scientists people in practice are actually using probably splatter
世界上的医生，他们非常准确，所以现在不像
这是给数学家或计算机科学家在实践中
this is for mathematicians or computer scientists people in practice are actually using probably splatter
实际上使用可能是飞溅的模型来预测所有
model for prognosis all the loss of diseases computer vision speech recognition Google Translate I
疾病的丧失计算机视觉语音识别Google翻译我的意思是我
mean I use it you know when I go to China I always say something
用它，你知道我去中国的时候我总是会说些什么，它翻译成
and it translates and I always see what it translates to be sure it was
而且我总是看到它的含义，以确保正确地系好它，因为
laced correctly because sometimes I say something and I read this like wow I'm gonna
有时我说些什么，我读起来就像哇，我会惹上麻烦
get in trouble and so it really works very well okay I mean I have
所以它真的很好用，好吧，我是说我看到它甚至在
seen it even working when there are several people speaking simultaneously with action and it
有几个人同时讲话和行动，它确实
does miracles so it's really a director filtration of republished graphical models practically every topic
奇迹，所以这真的是导演对重新发布的图形的过滤
模型几乎可以构成算法机器学习的每个主题
of the algorithm machine learning can be posed on probabilistic graphical models for okay so
在概率图形模型上可以，所以我们可能不知道
we may I don't know if we have
time I covered it with ideas of blatant holy Moses model reduction in the fall
在概率图形模型上可以，所以我们可能不知道
我在秋天用公然的圣洁的摩西模型减少的想法报道了它
so misspent electrocuted go back and
因此，用废纸电死的人可以回去解决海洋问题，使用
address the ocean generalize them using graphical model so if you don't know anything about
图形化模型，因此，如果您对哪种溶剂还不了解一无所知
what solvent is fine because when we post them in graphic we will post them
因为当我们以图形形式发布它们时，我们会将它们发布为新问题，因此
as new problems and so you will see sort of a modern aspect of this
您会看到这种算法的现代方面，我想您知道
algorithm and and I think you know
you like of more than a questions that without the means to visualizer the you
您会看到这种算法的现代方面，我想您知道
您不仅仅喜欢一个问题，而没有一个可视化您自己的方法
know error control codes and the way you
知道错误控制代码以及了解计算机的方式，然后重新启动并
know your computer you know restart and figure out what goes wrong right and and
找出哪里出了错，然后正确地将其真正建立在
became properly it's really based in in
probabilistic graphical models if you take for most in engineering to take sort of you
找出哪里出了错，然后正确地将其真正建立在
概率图形模型（如果您在工程学中占多数）
probabilistic graphical models if you take for most in engineering to take sort of you
有点您知道我们谈论的很少
know we talked about little to
undividable scanner there but actually the source of this adapter ones can be extremely effective
有点您知道我们谈论的很少
那里无法分割的扫描仪，但实际上该适配器的来源可以是
undividable scanner there but actually the source of this adapter ones can be extremely effective
对于这些知识非常有效，它们不仅是随机变量，而且
for this knowledge they're not simply random variables but the interconnected complicated systems of differing
相互联系的复杂系统，具有不同的生物学和力学模型
ology and mechanical model the thermal model etc and each of them has its own
热模型等，威尔逊内部的每个模型都有其自己的随机性
random by the Wilson within right but you have interconnected systems that speak to each
是的，但是您有相互通信的系统，并且
other and this is really sort of an important area for development because it points
这确实是一个重要的发展领域，因为它指出了很多
a lot of tolerances because a lot of these systems are governed by models that
公差，因为这些系统中有很多是由以下模型控制的：
are very compassionate very expensive so so a lot of the methodologies for doing inference
非常富有同情心，非常昂贵，所以很多方法
would not be able to sort of
推理将无法直接解决您必须要做的事情
what directly you would have to do something there to simplify the representation of these
那里有一些东西可以简化这些系统的表示，所以
systems okay so let's you know go fast through the patient knowledge of the variables
让我们知道通过患者对存在变量的了解来快速了解
exist already said for publicity Lester the lock opens it basically will provide information on
已经说过，为了宣传Lester，锁将基本打开
有关独立关系的信息，因此嫁接具有多个节点
independence relations so graft has a number of nodes as a number of edges the
如果我们有一个
number of nodes from want to be the number of edges if we have a
directed graph basically would be this
如果我们有一个
有向图基本上是这对逗号T，否则
pair s comma T where the else goes from the you know the arrow goes
你知道箭头现在变成凸面了，真的，你知道扩展这个
convexity okay now to really you know extend this the bottom directed and directed graphs
底部有向图和有向图必须使用所谓的
you have to use what's called an
adjacency matrix so if you define the  adjacency matrix
底部有向图和有向图必须使用所谓的
邻接矩阵，所以如果您定义邻接矩阵
adjacency matrix so if you define the  adjacency matrix
如果广告的逗号T在此集合中，则GF标普小写注释等于1
GF S&amp;P little notes equals one if the ads s comma T is in this
set all right and this allows you to extend this to undirected graphs because if
如果广告的逗号T在此集合中，则GF标普小写注释等于1
这使您可以将其扩展到无向图，因为如果您有G
you have G of s comma T equal 12 and simultaneous in G of T
s的逗号T等于12，同时在T的X的G中等于1，然后
comma X equal to 1 right then
this is an undirected graph there is no going from s to T and T
s的逗号T等于12，同时在T的X的G中等于1，然后
这是一个无向图，从s到T没有变化，T 2 s相同
2 s is the same okay so two examples and I threw a lot so
好的，所以有两个例子，到目前为止，我在这里投入了很多术语，
far terminology here that's going to
come in the following slides but it helps to see them several times so you
好的，所以有两个例子，到目前为止，我在这里投入了很多术语，
进入以下幻灯片，但可以多次查看它们，因此您
have note one two three four five I am
有注一二三四有五我要打注一路全
going to call note one the road all right can you give me without rocks
是的，您能给我没有障碍的东西，甚至只是阅读拉动式滑梯吗？
or even reading the pull up slides just look on the graph what do you
在图表上看，您认为路线是什么，我的意思不是很好
think the route will be I mean wouldn't be a good this mixture I mean
这种混合物，我的意思是你注意到好吗？
you notice okay there is from you
know so so in other ways why you know the route is of five and
这种混合物，我的意思是你注意到好吗？
以其他方式知道，为什么你知道这条路线是五条，这就是
it's one what will be a good definition
将是一个很好的定义
对，所以在这种情况下，我在这里重复了一个答案
right so so so I am repeating the answer here in this case one has
not lost coming to it okay and as we will see this implies following in
对，所以在这种情况下，我在这里重复了一个答案
可以了，正如我们将看到的，这意味着下面的定义
definitions when I come up with one has no father okay and with a definition
当我想出一个没有父亲好吗
有五个定义，那就是图5的本质。
five them that is the nature of the graph five has no children okay so
孩子们好吗，所以五个并没有简单地发送一个是
five has not simply sent one is
the ornament of - all right and three you know here you know 40s -
孩子们好吗，所以五个并没有简单地发送一个是
装饰物-好吧，三个你知道，这里你知道40多岁-力量是
the ornament of - all right and three you know here you know 40s -
两个和三个还可以，并实现其他目标
power is two and three okay etc and to achieve what else to come together
在一起很重要，它又会再次出现，但是我想
is important and it phase again this is coming up later but I want you
to see hundreds of times so we can
在一起很重要，它又会再次出现，但是我想
您看到了数百次，因此我们可以进行交流，这说明了
communicate it says this directed a means it has no cycles of a cyclic graph
表示它没有循环图的周期
all right you noticed has no better it has no cycles someone would say this
你注意到没有更好，没有周期有人会说这是周期
is a cycle but actually because this is the electric graph you notice when I
但这实际上是因为这是您在我进去时注意到的电图
go the direction of the arrows here I cannot go from four to three so
箭头的方向在这里我不能从四个变到三个
there are no cycles them okay
所以没有周期，他们还好吧，所以我们讨论了这个，然后
alright so we discussed this and then it says the notes are number in topological
说音符是按拓扑顺序编号的，所以这并不意味着看起来非常
order so what does not mean looks very
sensual for the left graph what do we mean - political order just looking at
说音符是按拓扑顺序编号的，所以这并不意味着看起来非常
左图是感性的，我们的意思是什么-政治秩序只是看
this graph basically what will be sort
该图基本上将是您的想象力与我们分享的内容，因此
of your imagination share with us so the  numbering change in topological order so
编号按拓扑顺序更改，因此
我的意思是抱怨我总是一二三四五
I mean complain I have always one two three four five
好的，传统的听力有点好，因为我们定义了通往
all right the tradition hearing bit right which since we define the route to be
the note that has no parents all
好的，传统的听力有点好，因为我们定义了通往
是没有父母没事的音符，所以基本上我们必须开始
right so basically we have to start numbering from the root to the leaves basically
从根到叶的编号基本上没问题，这是一种拓扑
okay and that's a topological order not to more complicated God you know this may
为了不更复杂的上帝，你知道这可能不是唯一的
not be a unique topological order all right but you start majestically you are not
拓扑顺序还可以，但是您雄伟地开始了，您不会
going to assign to the chain to the children notice that they're in the order
分配给孩子链注意，他们按照以下顺序
of numbering on the part right number the parents and the children that's the idea
正确编号的部分就是给父母和孩子编号
好吧，所以2＆3是孩子，所以1会
here okay so 2 &amp; 3 are the children so 1 will be there to
在那里进入它将类似地有这些是的父母
enter it will be there similarly these are the parents of course draw the numbering
当然，绘制拓扑顺序编号现在可以使同一张图有意义
of topological order makes sense ok the same graph now if it was an undirected
如果这是一个无向图，那么我正在浇注很多东西
graph okay these I'm pouring and lots of things because you know I want you
因为你知道我要你看到那些东西
to see those things hundreds of times and I'm details that are going to be
数百次，我将要讨论的细节很多
discussed with lots of simple examples in coop lectures right but I want you to
合作社讲座中的一些简单示例，但我希望您现在看到这些内容
see these things now so in some sense I'm claiming that the gallop you see
所以从某种意义上讲，我声称您在这里看到的驰op非常
here it is very much the
same as that job but they see there is something going on that's a little
所以从某种意义上讲，我声称您在这里看到的驰op非常
和那个工作一样，但是他们看到有些事情正在发生
bit different what's the difference between the two block when you look at them okay
不同，当您看着它们时，两个块之间有什么区别
there are no arrows but there is
没有箭头，但还有其他不同之处，那又是什么
something else that is different so what is definitely when you visually look at this
绝对是当您直观地看到这两个和三个相互连接时
two and three are connected and that's an essential step when you go from directly
当您从直接草稿中撤出时，这是必不可少的步骤，因此
drafts from directed so what are the two and three note what is common between
二和三是什么，请注意二和三之间有什么共同点
two and three their parent just know the
父母只知道
他们的力量点，那么当您从有向图转到UM时
their points of what of power so when you went from a directed graph to
UM directive what you need to do is you need to be sure the parents
他们的力量点，那么当您从有向图转到UM时
指示您需要做的是确保父母已结婚
are married because this is not today we don't allow Mary power okay so we
因为今天不是今天，我们不允许Mary拥有权力，所以我们嫁给所有人
marry them all right and this process methodical is called a modernization process okay people
正确的，这个过程有条不紊被称为现代化过程
who think that I'm you know my
认为我是您的人知道我让您猜测宗教含义，但是
let you guess religious connotations but that's the terminology moralization okay so you basically have
那是术语道德化，所以您基本上必须嫁给
父母很好，实际上你马上就可以看到
to marry the parents okay and actually immediately you can see when you marry the
当您嫁给父母时，您会在此图中移动
parents you get moved in this graph okay so suddenly you went from no loops
好吧，突然之间，您从无循环转到了正确且明显的两个循环
to two loops right and and obvious
implications in the way we're going to treat this process now in the graphs once
好吧，突然之间，您从无循环转到了正确且明显的两个循环
现在我们将在图中处理这一过程的方式产生影响
you moralize you marry the parts
一旦道德化，就将第二部分和第三部分结合在一起，我们就定义了整个整体
two and three we define what this whole page and if particularly of interest here
页面，如果特别感兴趣，这里就是所谓的最大集团
is what is called maximal cliques
okay so click is a set of interconnected no okay so for example if you
页面，如果特别感兴趣，这里就是所谓的最大集团
好的，因此单击是一组相互关联的操作不好，例如，如果您是
this is one two or three is a clique right because one is connected to
一二或三是集团权利，因为一个连接到一个平方
one squared - 3 + 2 is correct - 3 all the nodes are connected
-3 + 2是正确的-3所有节点都已连接，现在您说是1 2 3和
now you say is 1 2 3 and
privately why not one employee without connected right 2 + 5 3 &amp; 5 are
-3 + 2是正确的-3所有节点都已连接，现在您说是1 2 3和
私下为什么没有一名员工没有关联权2 +
not correct ok so 1 2 &amp; 3 2
5 3＆5是不正确的，所以他们称我们为1 2＆3 2 3＆4＆3＆5
3 &amp; 4 &amp; 3 &amp; 5 of what they call we called maxima please
请给我打电话，我可以告诉你，这会进来
and I can tell you and this will come in
four five lectures I don't know the idea of identifying this parchment which will be
请给我打电话，我可以告诉你，这会进来
四五堂课，我不知道识别羊皮纸的想法
but when we take a joint probability
但是，当我们采用本段的联合概率分布时，
distribution of this paragraph around the variables we're going to be able to write the
我们将能够将联合分布写为的变量
joint distribution as the product of potentials is with this potential behind on our table
潜力的产品在我们的桌子上有这个潜力
please so the local potentials what its potential would be on automatically and that would
所以当地的潜力会自动发挥出来，
这实际上将是一个惊人的定理，我们将要证明
be actually an amazing theorem which we are going to prove right but somehow if
是的，但是如果您有这样的图和概率分布，
you have a graph like that and a probability distribution defined on this graph then
在此图上定义，然后您可以将其分解为
that you can decompose it on potentials defined over this box conflicts okay again think
这个盒子有冲突，好吧，再想一想这是从
of this as start from the
air ideas because we will discuss those as we go in underneath a course okay
这个盒子有冲突，好吧，再想一想这是从
提出想法，因为我们将在课程学习过程中讨论这些想法，所以
so let's see the parents of a node all right you remember the conduit defining
让我们看一下节点的父级，您还记得管道定义
what was the name of G this is the
G的名字是什么，这是邻接矩阵，所以节点的父节点
adjacency matrix so the parent of a node s are all the node equal G
s是T逗号的所有等于G的节点s等于R，因此例如父级
of T comma s is equal to R so for example the parent of non-stick
are two and five okay and
s是T逗号的所有等于G的节点s等于R，因此例如父级
不粘的数是2和5可以，您可以将其表示为5等于
you can denote this as five six equal to point 5 or X 5 6
点5或X 5 6，您知道不同的符号，我认为这是参与的
you know different notations I think this is participating  both notations are the ones used by
这两种符号都是
迈克尔·乔丹（Michael Jordan）的东西，两个没有背心的日期基本上都是笔记叶
the Michael Jordan stuff the two dates of no vest are basically the notes leaf
touch of Geo Testament equal to one the
迈克尔·乔丹（Michael Jordan）的东西，两个没有背心的日期基本上都是笔记叶
地缘约等于老爬的好是最好的，
climbing of an old alright is best and the pairing suppressed and so I actually
配对被抑制了，所以我实际上一直在寻找，就像你知道为什么
what I was looking is like you know why
they don't like the children all right but somehow that's why maybe I never use
配对被抑制了，所以我实际上一直在寻找，就像你知道为什么
他们不喜欢孩子们，但是不知为何，所以也许我从不使用
the terminology commonly but until we
通常使用该术语，但是直到我们发现这是不正确的
find that this is not right in definition this is what it is there so
定义这就是那里的含义，所以家人被问及我们的各个部分
the family is asked and the parts of us
we already discussed route least the knows no parents to leave the know dot children
定义这就是那里的含义，所以家人被问及我们的各个部分
我们已经讨论过最少的路线，不认识的父母不离开知识点
the ancestors of an LP are all
孩子LP的祖先都是s的音符，而s的路径是
the notes s where there is a path from s to T and equal to
到T并等于有向图，如果有的话，该路径必须是有向路径
directed graph this path has to be a directed path if some directed basically any
定向从s到T的任何路径都可以做到，
path from s to T will do it and the descendants of an arrest are
all the nodes right but you
定向从s到T的任何路径都可以做到，
逮捕都是正确的节点，但是您可以找到从s到T的路径
can find the trail from s to T and again in the ref graphs this
在参考图中，我们必须遵循箭头的方向，所以这些是
trail we have to follow the arrow so these are the ancestors and goes to
祖先到中央[掌声]
the central the [Applause] neighborhoods and it doesn't matter what I will graph we have
街区，无论我要画什么，都可以立即得到
the immediately corrected note so the neighbors of s all the taste provided 0% equal
更正的音符，使s的所有邻居都提供了等于G之一的0％
to one of G of T of s equal to one okay so in defining
的T of s等于1可以，因此在定义给定的邻居时
the neighbors given even if it's a directed graph the orientation it's not important so
即使它是有向图的方向
这并不重要，所以节点的度数是邻居数
the degree of a node is the number of neighbors and in particular you would
特别是您会看到这一点，并且有很多穆斯林酵素的书在里里外外
see this and lots of Muslim leavening books the in-and-out degrees basically count the number
学位基本上计算父母的数量和孩子的数量，因此
of parents and the number of children so when they say the in degrees the
当他们说度数为父母数时，他们是度数为父母数
number of parents they are degrees the number of children and this is sort of
的孩子，这是一个重要的概念，因为当我们写
an important concept because when we write the joint probability distribution we would see the
联合概率分布，我们将看到因式分解仍将
factorization will still basically with this in degrees with a number of parents retaining I
基本上，在一定程度上，我保留了许多父母
may actually show you in the slide shortly we already discuss the concept of a
实际上在幻灯片中向您展示了，我们已经讨论了
directed cycle alright so in this
好吧，定向循环好，所以在此图中没有定向循环
diagram here there is no directed cycle but you notice from this this one okay
但是您从这一点注意到这一点，这没有一个定向周期
on this there is no directed cycle all
right so a directed Pacific Loft is a directed graph with non directed cycles okay
但是您从这一点注意到这一点，这没有一个定向周期
对，所以有向太平洋阁楼是有向环的有向图
right so a directed Pacific Loft is a directed graph with non directed cycles okay
好吧，我们将要使用的大多数图形
and most of the graphs we are going to
use will be direct the strictly graphs but you know when we generalized we will
好吧，我们将要使用的大多数图形
使用将是严格的图的直接图，但是您知道我们将其概括时，我们将
be able to go away without okay this
能够绕开而走不走这个原则三和直接进入
principle the three and the direct entry is very essential because algorithms on three are
是非常必要的，因为三个算法都可以实现
they just implement all right and you know we wish that every graph was a
而且您知道我们希望每个图都是三个，因为如果是三个，我们
three because if it's a three we
can do inference in second so this total would be an ideal situation so an
而且您知道我们希望每个图都是三个，因为如果是三个，我们
可以在第二秒做推断，所以这个总数将是一个理想的情况，因此
undirected three is an undirected graph
无向三是一个无向图，没有循环，并且对于
with no cycles all right and for an undirected tree there is a single path
无向树，任何一对节点之间都只有一条路径
between any pair of nodes okay
and I'm starting with this right because I would be to be able to define
无向树，任何一对节点之间都只有一条路径
我从这个权利开始，因为我将能够定义这个
this concept of 23 for directed graphs and with an internal directory strain on directory
23的概念，用于有向图，并带有内部目录应变
is an undirected graph with no
目录是没有循环的无向图，所以例如
cycles okay so for example did we have an undirected three stomach work without cycles
在这里没有周期的无方向的三项胃工作，所以这不好，然后我们
here so this is not good then we
have reading picture anyway specimen and don't see it and maybe we'll want to come
在这里没有周期的无方向的三项胃工作，所以这不好，然后我们
反正有阅读图片的标本，却看不到，也许我们想
alright for our way so you know
顺其自然吧，所以您知道目录没有循环，所以有一个
directory has no cycles so there is a single path from any pair of nodes
来自任何一对节点的单路径，现在有向三是有向三是
now a directed three is a directed three is a directed a strictly graph in
指向一个严格的图，其中每个节点最多具有一个国会
which every node has at most one Parliament can we tell me why do we
告诉我为什么我们要一位父母，以及如何与之联系
want one parent and how is that going to be connected with the modernization process
我提到的现代化过程
that I mentioned for it says the director 3 is a dog in which every
因为它说导演3是只狗，每条通知中最多只有一个部分
notice at most one part you
never are certified for there this equivalency of a directive three-wheeler on directly after we
因为它说导演3是只狗，每条通知中最多只有一个部分
从来没有在那里被证明的定向三轮车的等效性
never are certified for there this equivalency of a directive three-wheeler on directly after we
在我们进行了一些我们称之为道德化成功的操作之后，
did some operations which we called moralization success a directory is a dog in which
目录是一条狗，里面有西餐的每一个通知，为什么当局
every notice of Western palate so why the authorities think has one polished because it
认为有一个抛光，因为它有两个抛光，然后
has two polished then what is going to happen when we transform it to know
当我们将其转换为直接知道图时，我们将与那些结婚
directly graph we will marry those
parents and as a result we will get the site right so in directed three
当我们将其转换为直接知道图时，我们将与那些结婚
家长，因此我们将使网站正确无误，因此针对以下三个需求
needs to care everyone has at most one part okay now so this will be
现在照顾每个人最多都可以，所以这将是理想的情况
ideal situations right to have enough directly or the direction three now if we have
有权直接拥有足够的权利，或者如果我们已经指示，则现在拥有方向3
directed a strictly graphical just one on one parent right and we mobilize it effectively
严格的图形化一对一父母权利，我们动员了它
we will get you know we get
有效地，我们将使您知道我们得到了循环，但是如果无定向玻璃能够
cycles but if the undirected glass that we get is a tree all right then
我们得到的是一棵树，那么我们可以将其称为小马识别器
we can call this the recognizer for the pony  tree okay so let's see some examples  here
树好吧，让我们在这里看一些例子
你能告诉我这张图是火车是哪一列，而那棵树是一棵多树还是
can you tell me which one this graphs is a train which to one is
a poly-tree or you know what is this car is this Satori they're coming to
你能告诉我这张图是火车是哪一列，而那棵树是一棵多树还是
你知道这辆车是什么Satori他们来对了我们的定义吧
our definition right over there ft3 is very very noxious of most one pilot does
ft3对大多数飞行员来说非常有害
this loop to be like a tree right so this actually transform in eastern undirected
就是一棵树，所以它实际上在那里的东部无向图中变形
graph right there will be no novelization of step so the interconnect is not in
将不会是步骤的新颖性，因此互连不会在那儿，因为您
that because you know this just this is the part that has happened father so
知道这就是发生过的事情父亲
you have every not just one part so
因此，您不仅拥有每个部件，而且拥有一个平台
there would be a single platform everybody know to any other node so this 2
每个人都对其他任何节点都知道，所以现在这个2 3为什么是33看起来像
3 now why is this a 33 it looks like
in a simple tree but actually it's a 43 the reason is what this night
每个人都对其他任何节点都知道，所以现在这个2 3为什么是33看起来像
在一个简单的树中，但实际上是43，原因是今晚的
has how many product is 2 so when you merge them all right and you
许多乘积是2，所以当您合并它们时就可以了
而且您将其设为无向图，是的，每条路径都有一条路径
make this an undirected graph yes there is a single path from every node to
any other node but there is a
而且您将其设为无向图，是的，每条路径都有一条路径
节点到任何其他节点，但有一个循环可以
cycle there ok now obviously you know the algorithms will get a bit more complicated
现在很明显，您知道当您将算法变得更加复杂时，
有一个多叉树，但实际上当您将其转换为
when you have a poly-tree but actually when you transform this to the third form
of graph that I call it
有一个多叉树，但实际上当您将其转换为
图的第三种形式，我称它为意大利面图，但您会看到
the pasta graph but you will see that you can treat the 23 basically a
您可以治疗23基本上一分钱的树会在3时变成实际的
penny tree will become actually there at 3 okay and then you can apply the
好的，然后您可以应用标准算法，因此我们已经看到了此费用，
standard algorithm so we've seen this cost okay but you need to change the grade
但您需要更改图表的等级为四边形，所以现在考虑一下
the the graph is the quad so now think this would be a fantastic for
对于图来说，这将是一个奇妙的效果，这也将是非常奇妙的，因此
graphs look like that this will also be fantastic so it is more complicated but
它更复杂，但是以某种方式我们将能够让您知道开发
somehow we will be able to do you know develop algorithms that they have the
它们具有相同复杂度的算法
same complex this it will work okay so this is basically the same thing we
好吧，这基本上就是我们刚刚讨论的同一件事，也是同一件事
just discussed and the same thing
here so we talked about cliques and maximal cliques so there is this constant of
好吧，这基本上就是我们刚刚讨论的同一件事，也是同一件事
在这里，我们讨论了集团和最大集团，所以这是
a clique is only defined for
集团的常数仅针对无向图进行定义，再次为更多
undirected graphs and again a much more clique is the the highest number of interconnected
派系是互连节点数最多，数目最多的节点
nodes and highest number means you cannot go and consider adding another no to the
意味着您不能去考虑在集团中再加上一个否定
clique without violating the property okay so this would be an essential development sir charies
侵犯财产好吧，这将是必不可少的发展先生
当您动员它使它成为无向的时，将有理图
a directed graph when you mobilize this to make it an undirected graph that looks
看起来不错的图，如果我在这里结婚2和3会怎样？
like up okay so what what parents if I married here 2 &amp; 3 right
5 this pillow and that C 7 has how
看起来不错的图，如果我在这里结婚2和3会怎样？
对5这个枕头，C 7有多少父母拥有3票对
many parents has 3 votes right how's the post will have three parts well there's
帖子将分为三个部分，可以允许一些宗教，所以我们
some religion is allowed okay so we
marry for a 5 pollen sticks okay so alright and again you know I'm trying
帖子将分为三个部分，可以允许一些宗教，所以我们
嫁给5个花粉棒好吧，又一次，你知道我在努力
this just to treat from now but yeah
这只是从现在开始要治疗的，但是是的，我们将详细讨论这一点。
we're going to discuss this in details right so you know just remember what this
是的，所以您只需要记住这个组织过程意味着什么，
process of organization means and somehow we haven't proved the district we will into this
不知何故我们还没有证明我们将进入这个地区，无论您知道什么
and whatever you know how many I said well equivalent means right so we will
我说了多少对等的意思是对的，所以当我们讨论时，我们会看到
see when we discussed about optimization of the joint probability distribution - gross alright so
关于联合概率分布的优化
-好吧，好吧，高速公路就是正确的目标，让我毫无保留地给你
highways the goal right so let me give you without any prints or anything like
打印或类似的东西好吧，因为我们会回到这个
that okay because we will come back to this I would join probably distribution of
将加入这七个变量的分布，因为它们基于
this seven variables is they compose based on the graph that you see okay so
您看到的图表还可以，因此下一个1到7的符号表示这是
the notation next one to seven means this is the joint probability electronic Stewart seven
联合概率电子斯图尔特七号，现在，如果我们有右图
and now if we have a graph right
and somebody gives you the the you know P effects want to at seven the
联合概率电子斯图尔特七号，现在，如果我们有右图
有人给你，你知道P效应要在七个理论上
theory tells you what's the what is going to be the right hand side I
告诉你什么是右手边
mean without looking at this right so
我的意思是不看这个权利就不要看这个
you don't look at this what is to improve ability relates to join of variables
一键提高与两个效果变量的连接有关的能力
of the two effects one touch
seven varieties will be north x one times what the effect is even worth after
一键提高与两个效果变量的连接有关的能力
七个品种将成为北方x效果甚至是值得的一倍
and and p53 given x1 x2 etc now if
之后和和p53给定x1 x2等，如果您注意到一般要求的话，那就是
you notice general claiming well it's actually much simpler that states P of x1 times
实际上要简单得多，在给定X 3的X 1 P的情况下，将x的P乘以x 2的P
P of x2 given X 1 P of X 3
given X 1 P notice that in the worst case there are like three arguments
实际上要简单得多，在给定X 3的X 1 P的情况下，将x的P乘以x 2的P
给定X 1 P，请注意，在最坏的情况下，
in the condition can look at the graph to look at this equation and tells
条件可以看图看这个方程式，然后再告诉我 什么都没有感觉到我在监视，你能看一下吗
me again I'm feeling nothing like I'm spying is there and can you look at
this and somehow imagine what the God tells you  but somehow it's not first this equation  without integration
条件可以看图看这个方程式，然后再告诉我 什么都没有感觉到我在监视，你能看一下吗
以某种方式想像上帝告诉你的东西，但是以某种方式不是这等式的第一
this and somehow imagine what the God tells you  but somehow it's not first this equation  without integration
没有整合
好吧，从根本上来说，服务巴瑟斯特是如此，每架都是直升飞机
well it's so basically if service Bathurst is so every which is a copter and
in this case this parcel is a
好吧，从根本上来说，服务巴瑟斯特是如此，每架都是直升飞机
在这种情况下，这个包裹是一个概率，是一个条件概率
probability is a conditional probability distribution of the the variable in that note conditioned on
该笔记中变量的分布以其父代为条件，所以在这里我
its parent so here I have the probability of X 1 conditioned on the parents
有X 1的概率以X 1的父母为条件
of X 1 what parents each
one has no extradition apparent which is one extreme condition the parents which is one
有X 1的概率以X 1的父母为条件
一个人没有引渡的迹象，这是父母的一种极端情况，
one has no extradition apparent which is one extreme condition the parents which is one
是除12个条件之外的一个，父母是固定的2＆3上的2 X部落
except 12 condition the parents which is 2 X tribe on 2 &amp; 3 that's
fixed on 5 &amp; 3 &amp; at 7 on 4 5 &amp; 6 now the
是除12个条件之外的一个，父母是固定的2＆3上的2 X部落
现在在5＆3和7在4 5＆6
reason that this looks way simpler run the what the product will repel you write
更简单的运行，产品会击退您第一次写信给我们的人
the people first time we have actually said one condition of x1 x2 x3 x4
实际上已经说过x1 x2 x3 x4 x5 x6的一种情况
x5 x6 the fact that you don't
have X 1 X 2 X 3 X 2 X 3 means that X 7
实际上已经说过x1 x2 x3 x4 x5 x6的一种情况
X 1 X 2 X 3 X 2 X 3表示X 7​​独立于变量X 1 X 2
is independent of the variables X 1 X 2
X 3 given the variables X 4 X 5 vs. now I have no proof
X 1 X 2 X 3 X 2 X 3表示X 7​​独立于变量X 1 X 2
X 3给定变量X 4 X 5与现在的I
X 3 given the variables X 4 X 5 vs. now I have no proof
没有任何证据，我只是在告诉我们这样做的答案是什么
anything I'm just telling what the answers would be when we do the proof okay
so somehow look at the graph
没有任何证据，我只是在告诉我们这样做的答案是什么
证明还可以，所以以某种方式查看该图，您应该可以立即
you should be able to immediately just from the graph presented the composition that you
从图中呈现出您知道是正确的构图
know is the correct decomposition so here I have to do calculations by chant and
分解，所以在这里我必须按吟进行计算并尝试10
try for 10 hours and addition so that you know  immediately with that perform this and
小时和加法，以便您立即知道执行该操作和
您知道我们是否有七个变量，每个变量取K
this you know you know if we had seven variables and each variable takes K
重视没有独立关系的权利，我需要五个来
values the with no independence relations right I'm gonna need five to the seventh to
第七个描述左边的联合概率分布
describe the joint probability distribution on the left hand side but you noticed requiring sort
手边，但您注意到需要排序几率表
of probability tables Hotel smaller size so let's say P X 1 you need K
酒店较小，因此假设PX 1需要影响K值才能得出
values be affected to give an
extra on K square I'm not a counting here for the harmonization of this probabilities
酒店较小，因此假设PX 1需要影响K值才能得出
在K平方上有多余的部分，在这里我不算是这个的统一
make like is e this is K 3
概率使得像e是K 3并且这是K 4所以基本上如果我们有
and this is K 4 so basically if we have independence relations that you see
您在图中看到的独立关系我们还没有真正证明过
in the graph we haven't really proved anything again I emphasized this is lecture wrong
我再强调一遍，这是一次错误的演讲，只是吓you了你，所以你
to just scare you so you
can not come on closely but this it's K to the fourth versus if you
我再强调一遍，这是一次错误的演讲，只是吓you了你，所以你
不能接近，但这是K到第四位，如果没有
have no independence at all which would be K to the sub okay so independence
完全是独立的，那么就好了，所以独立关系
relations and independence relations in the graph G no imply from the talk but let's
图G中的独立性和独立性关系并不意味着谈话，而是说
say no two and three are not linked right two and seven are not linked
没有两个和三个没有联系起来，正确的两个和七个没有联系上政治
politics on of being one is definitely so this lot of edges between knowledge is
成为一体绝对是知识之间的诸多优势
what leads to this factorization and that's very nice because you can read it on
进行分解，这非常好，因为您可以在
the clock because each of these  distributions is a factor of the  probability of hits note from this  knowledge part
时钟，因为这些分布中的每一个都是
该知识部分中命中笔记的概率
the clock because each of these  distributions is a factor of the  probability of hits note from this  knowledge part
145那是我们应该完成所有事情的时候，所以我将继续
145 that's when we supposed to finish all right so I'm going to continue on
this lecture with a few more examples
145那是我们应该完成所有事情的时候，所以我将继续
本讲课还有更多示例，然后我们将慢慢进行，
and then we will take things slowly and discuss all the details on directed graphs
讨论有向图的所有细节，我们将从那里开始
and we will move from there
so the website I will try to put the neck strap at the latest way
讨论有向图的所有细节，我们将从那里开始
所以我明天会在网站上尝试用最新的方式戴上颈带
tomorrow we've had the latest by tomorrow okay and and actually I'm going to tend
到明天为止我们已经拥有了最新的，实际上我将倾向于
to those register and when I sent a copy of at least paper Bakula chapter
那些寄存器，当我从
from Jordans butcher you can start reading  them all right so I'll see you on  Thursday
Jordans屠夫，您可以开始阅读所有内容，以便我继续 周四